asianplayboy.com 2017-04-08

# ABCs Of Attraction | Privacy Policy

The ABCs of Attraction is committed to protecting your privacy and  
developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online  
experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to The ABCs of  
Attraction Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using  
The ABCs of Attraction website, you consent to the data practices  
described in this statement.

## Collection of your Personal Information

The ABCs of Attraction collects personally identifiable information,  
such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone  
number. The ABCs of Attraction also collects anonymous demographic  
information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age,  
gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software  
that is automatically collected by The ABCs of Attraction. This  
information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names,  
access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is  
used by The ABCs of Attraction for the operation of the service, to  
maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics  
regarding use of The ABCs of Attraction Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally  
identifiable information or personally sensitive data through The ABCs  
of Attraction public message boards, this information may be collected  
and used by others. Note: The ABCs of Attraction does not read any of  
your private online communications.

The ABCs of Attraction encourages you to review the privacy statements  
of Web sites you choose to link to from The ABCs of Attraction so that  
you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your  
information. The ABCs of Attraction is not responsible for the privacy  
statements or other content on Web sites outside of The ABCs of  
Attraction and The ABCs of Attraction family of Web sites.

### Use of your Personal Information

The ABCs of Attraction collects and uses your personal information to  
operate The ABCs of Attraction Web site and deliver the services you  
have requested. The ABCs of Attraction also uses your personally  
identifiable information to inform you of other products or services  
available from The ABCs of Attraction and its affiliates. The ABCs of  
Attraction may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about  
your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may  
be offered.

The ABCs of Attraction does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists  
to third parties. The ABCs of Attraction may, from time to time,  
contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular  
offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique  
personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone  
number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, The ABCs  
of Attraction may share data with trusted partners to help us perform  
statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer  
support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are  
prohibited from using your personal information except to provide  
these services to The ABCs of Attraction, and they are required to  
maintain the confidentiality of your information.

The ABCs of Attraction does not use or disclose sensitive personal  
information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations,  
without your explicit consent.

The ABCs of Attraction keeps track of the Web sites and pages our  
customers visit within The ABCs of Attraction, in order to determine  
what The ABCs of Attraction services are the most popular. This data  
is used to deliver customized content and advertising within The ABCs  
of Attraction to customers whose behavior indicates that they are  
interested in a particular subject area.

The ABCs of Attraction Web sites will disclose your personal  
information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in  
the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to  
the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The ABCs  
of Attraction or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or  
property of The ABCs of Attraction; and, (c) act under exigent  
circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The ABCs of  
Attraction, or the public.

#### Use of Cookies

The ABCs of Attraction Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize  
your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your  
hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs  
or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to  
you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued  
the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience  
feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web  
server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you  
personalize The ABCs of Attraction pages, or register with The ABCs of  
Attraction site or services, a cookie helps The ABCs of Attraction to  
recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies  
the process of recording your personal information, such as billing  
addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same  
The ABCs of Attraction Web site, the information you previously  
provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use The ABCs of  
Attraction features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers  
automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser  
setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline  
cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive  
features of the The ABCs of Attraction services or Web sites you  
visit.

##### Security of your Personal Information

The ABCs of Attraction secures your personal information from  
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. The ABCs of Attraction secures  
the personally identifiable information you provide on computer  
servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from  
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information  
(such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it  
is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket  
Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Changes to this Statement**  
The ABCs of Attraction will occasionally update this Statement of  
Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. The ABCs of  
Attraction encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be  
informed of how The ABCs of Attraction is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**  
The ABCs of Attraction welcomes your comments regarding this Statement  
of Privacy. If you believe that The ABCs of Attraction has not adhered  
to this Statement, please contact The ABCs of Attraction at  
support@abcofattraction.com.com. We will use commercially reasonable  
efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

Need help?    
Call our full time Customer Service Representative tollfree at   
1-323-317-2431  
Monday-Friday 12pm-5pm PST
